Sometimes the only way to self-improve is to self-destruct.
Harmontown is a documentary film directed by Neil Berkeley.
A comedic, brutally honest documentary following self-destructive TV writer
Dan Harmon as he takes his live podcast on a national tour.
Self, played by Dan Harmon.
Self, played by Erin McGathy.
Self, played by Jeff Bryan Davis.
Self, played by Steve Agee.
Self, played by Jack Black.
Self, played by Joel McHale.
Harmontown is a comedy podcast that aired weekly from
June 16, 2012 to December 3, 2019.
It was hosted by writer Dan Harmon, best known as the creator of the television series
Community and the co-creator of Rick and Morty, along with actor Jeff B.
Davis, best known for his work on the improvisational
comedy series Whose Line Is It Anyway?
Harmontown began as a monthly live comedy show in Los Angeles, California, at the NerdMelt Showroom
on May 23, 2011, but the show became weekly after Harmon was fired from Community.
Since mid-2012, each episode of Harmontown had been recorded and released as a podcast,
first by Feral Audio through 2017, then Starburns Audio starting in 2018.
The podcast featured many guest appearances, including Game Grumps, Emily V.
Gordon, Kumail Nanjiani, Greg Proops, Aubrey Plaza, Bobcat Goldthwait, Rob Schrab, Curtis Armstrong, Patton Oswalt, Jason Sudeikis, Dana
Carvey, Felicia Day, Robin Williams, Mitch Hurwitz, Joel McHale, Rob Corddry, John Mayer, Eric Idle, Logic, and Steve Agee.
On March 8, 2014, a documentary about the podcast,
premiered at the South by Southwest Film Festival.
The tone is dark.